const questionnaire = [
    {
      question:'My name is ?',
      answer:['Jessica', 'Vanessa', 'Melissa'],
      correct:'Jessica',
      questionId: "1"   
    },
    {
        question:'My second name is ?',
        answer:['Louisa', 'Antonella', 'Sofia'],
        correct:'Sofia',
        questionId: "2"  
    },
    {
        question:'My favourite color is ?',
        answer:['Green', 'Purple', 'Yellow'],
        correct:'Yellow',
        questionId: "3"  
    },
    {
        question:'My favourite fruit ?',
        answer:['Cherry', 'Apple', 'Mango'],
        correct:'Mango',
        questionId: "4" 
    },
    {
        question:'My favourite animal ?',
        answer:['Tiger', 'Cat', 'Lion'],
        correct:'Tiger', 
        questionId: "5"
    },
    {
        question:'My month birthday is ?',
        answer:['October', 'September', 'November'],
        correct:'October' ,
        questionId: "6"
    },
    {
        question:'My favourite series ?',
        answer:['Orange is the new black', 'The Good place', 'Friends'],
        correct:'Orange is the new black',
        questionId: "7"
    },
    {
        question:'I usually drink ?',
        answer:['Water', 'Vodka', 'Bier'],
        correct:'Water' ,
        questionId: "8"
    },
    {
        question:'The name of my first cat is ?',
        answer:['Cramique', 'Madara', 'Lady'],
        correct:'Cramique' ,
        questionId: "9"  
    },
    {
        question:'The name of my boyfriend is ?',
        answer:['Andy', 'Zachary', 'Luis'],
        correct:'Zachary' ,
        questionId: "10"  
    },
    {
        question:'I have never been to ?',
        answer:['Perou', 'Swiss', 'Danemark'],
        correct:'Danemark' ,
        questionId: "11"  
    },
    {
        question:"I don't like ?",
        answer:['Cooking', 'Cleaning my room', "Cleaning the cat's toilet"],
        correct:"Cleaning the cat's toilet" ,
        questionId: "12"  
    },
    {
        question:"I dance on ?",
        answer:['Hip Hop', 'Zumba', 'Reggae'],
        correct:'Zumba' ,
        questionId: "13"  
    },
    {
        question:"My default ?",
        answer:['Stubborn', 'Bad player', "Shy"],
        correct:"Stubborn" ,
        questionId: "14"  
    },
    {
        question:"My city ?",
        answer:['Lima', 'Caracas', "Bogota"],
        correct:"Caracas" ,
        questionId: "15"  
    }
];

//const question = questions[0];

export default questionnaire;